icheckemail.com 2013-03-28

# Maps Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the

http://www.imapdirections.com and imapdirections.com and governs data collection and usage. For

the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to imapdirections.com

include http://www.imapdirections.com, imapdirections.com and http://www.imapdirections.com. The

imapdirections.com website is a Translation Toolbar Review site. By using the imapdirections.com

website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Affiliate Status

http://www.imapdirections.com is an affiliate of Neverblue. http://www.imapdirections.com is an advertising service and is not associated with nor does it claim to represent any of the brands or merchants listed on this site. These brands and merchants in no way endorse http://www.imapdirections.com.

Collection of your Personal Information

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or

non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by

imapdirections.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names,

access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the

service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the

imapdirections.com website.

imapdirections.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link

to from imapdirections.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share

your information. imapdirections.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content

on websites outside of the imapdirections.com website.

Use of Cookies

The imapdirections.com website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience.

A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be

used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you,

and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The

purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For

example, if you personalize imapdirections.com pages, or register with imapdirections.com site or

services, a cookie helps imapdirections.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses,

shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same imapdirections.com website, the

information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the imapdirections.com

features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept

cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you

choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the

imapdirections.com services or websites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

imapdirections.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

Children Under Thirteen

imapdirections.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children

under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian

for permission to use this website.

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of

certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from

imapdirections.com by contacting us here:

-Web page: contact.imapdirections.com

-Email: contact (at) imapdirections.com

Changes to this Statement

imapdirections.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and

customer feedback. imapdirections.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be

informed of how imapdirections.com is protecting your information.

Contact Information

imapdirections.com welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If

you believe that imapdirections.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact

imapdirections.com at:

imapdirections.com

660 4th St. #109

San Francisco, California 94107

Email Address:

Contact (at) imapdirections.com

Effective as of January 24, 2013
